

magditiea@gmail.com | 226-759-5872 | Windsor ON

## Summary

Recent graduate of Carleton University's Coding Bootcamp. I'm a hard working, young and patient Sudanese entrepreneur who has one year of University(business), one senior level Full Stack Web Development course and currently taking two senior level database programs to improve my skills in mongoDB and mongoose. I love business/coding and my passion grows everyday. Fluent in english and arabic also currently learning Spanish. I am mobile and able to travel for work related purposes. Feel free to contact me about work through my phone number or email above.

## Skills

- Marketing expertise
- Leadership
- Problem-solving
- Cost management
- Business Planning
- Data entry

- Time management
- Friendly, positive attitude
- Databases
- Website analytics tools
- Wireframes
- Project management

## Experience

Ground Effects | Windsor, ON

**Production Associate** 

05/2021 - 06/2021

• Operated machinery, managed raw material and logged production data.

BioBest | Leamington, ON **Production Worker** 

12/2020 - 03/2021

• Calibrated and adjusted equipment using tools such as calipers, micrometers, height gauges, protractors and ring gauges.

Call Center Representative

06/2018 - 08/2018

Sutherland Global Services | Windsor, ON • Consulted with customers to determine best methods to resolve service and billing issues.

## **Education and Training**

University of Prince Edward Island | Charlottetown, PE **BBA** in Business Administration 04/2019

Carleton University | Online Graduate Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development 05/2021

Udemy 2021 Full-Stack Web Development Course | Online Graduate Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development